A Guide to the Harry Flood Byrd, Sr. Papers
Special Collections, University of Virginia Library
- Series IV: Miscellaneous Topics
  - F. Speeches and Statements
    - 3. Harry Flood Byrd's Public Statements and Press Releases
      - Federal Personnel. June - July, 1951, 1951 August 30 (Box Box 407)
      - Senator Byrd submitting Report of Finance Committee on H. R. 4014, 1951 September 5 (Box Box 407)
      - In connection with the case of Brig. Gen. David J. Crawford, 1951 September 7 (Box Box 407)
      - Response to the President's remarks at the dedication of the New G. A. O. Building, 1951 September 11 (Box Box 407)
      - On the resignation of General Marshall, 1951 September 12 (Box Box 407)
      - Hearing on the subject of Federal Expenditure Control, 1951 September 26 (Box Box 407)
      - Federal Personnel. July - August, 1951, 1951 October 2 (Box Box 407)
      - Federal Personnel. September, 1951, 1951 November 3 (Box Box 407)
      - On the death of Senator Wherry, 1951 November 29 (Box Box 407)
      - Reorganization of the Internal Revenue, 1952 January 24 (Box Box 407)
      - Federal Personnel and Pay. December 1951, 1952 February 4 (Box Box 407)
      - On changing the name of the Blue Ridge Parkway, 1952 February 26 (Box Box 407)
      - Endorsing Senator Russell for the Presidency, 1952 February 28 (Box Box 407)
      - Federal Payments to Individuals and Grants in Aid to States and Localities, 1952 March 3 (Box Box 407)
      - Establishment of Internal Revenue Bureau at Richmond, 1952 March 28 (Box Box 407)
      - On the withdrawal of the President from the presidential race, 1952 March 31 (Box Box 407)
      - Federal Personnel and Pay. February 1952, 1952 April 1 (Box Box 407)
      - Steel Strike, 1952 April 9 (Box Box 407)
      - Announcing candicacy for re-election, 1952 April 10 (Box Box 407)
      - King William County Anniversary, 1952 April 25 (Box Box 407)
      - On amendments to F. S. A. Appropriation and Post Office Appropriation Bills, 1952 April 29 (Box Box 407)
      - Federal Personnel. February - March, 1952, 1952 May 1 (Box Box 407)
      - On the case of General Francis T. Dodd, 1952 May 22 (Box Box 407)
      - Federal Personnel. April, 1952, 1952 June 3 (Box Box 407)
      - Seizure of the Steel Plants, 1952 June 10 (Box Box 407)
      - Statement given to A. P. on the Steel Strike. (Folder empty when processed), 1952 June 11 (Box Box 407)
      - Memorandum to Byrd Managers in Tobacco Counties, 1952 June 20 (Box Box 407)
      - Refuting statements made by Whitehead on agricultural record, 1952 June 23 (Box Box 407)
      - Unexpended balances as of June 30, 1952, 1952 June 29 (Box Box 407)
      - Unexpended Balances, 1952 June 30 (Box Box 407)
      - On the so-called Thomas Leave Amendment, 1952 June (Box Box 407)
      - On the Campaign, 1952 July 13 (Box Box 407)
      - Federal Personnel. May - June, 1952, 1952 August 6 (Box Box 407)
      - Federal Personnel and Pay. June - July, 1952, 1952 September 5 (Box Box 407)
      - Federal Personnel and Pay. July - August, 1952 October 3 (Box Box 407)
      - Memorandum sent to Virginia Editors in regard to decisions of the Attorneys General of Virginia, 1952 October 17 (Box Box 407)
      - On Senator's name being filed for Vice President, 1952 November 2 (Box Box 407)
      - On when the Senate convenes, 1952 November 10 (Box Box 407)
      - On the appointment of Mr. George Humphries as Secretary of the Treasury, 1952 November 21 (Box Box 407)
      - In regard to appointment as Member of the New Cabinet, 1952 November 21 (Box Box 407)
      - Statement and Report on Federal Civilian Employment Overseas, 1952 December 7 (Box Box 407)
      - On the tax outlook, 1952 December (Box Box 407)
      - On tax exemption for the incoming President and Vice President, 1953 January 3 (Box Box 407)
      - On Civilian employment. October - November, 1952, 1953 January 3 (Box Box 407)
      - Report by the Joint Committee on Reduction of Non-Essential Expenditures on Unexpended Balances, 1953 January 28 (Box Box 407)
      - On the President's State of the Union Message, 1953 February 2 (Box Box 407)
      - On the so-called single appropration bill, 1953 February 4 (Box Box 407)
      - Federal Personnel. November - December, 1952, 1953 February 5 (Box Box 407)
      - On abolishing the R. F. C., 1953 February 13 (Box Box 407)
      - Letter to Secretary Wilson in regard to shortage of ammunitions in Korea, 1953 March 5 (Box Box 407)
      - On the Van Fleet testimony before Armed Services Committee, 1953 March 10 (Box Box 407)
      - Resolution offered by Senator Byrd in Armed Services Committee, 1953 March 12 (Box Box 407)
      - Committee Print #3 with Memorandum and Statement of March 18, 1953 March 17 (Box Box 407)
      - Resolution for investigation of shortage of ammunition, 1953 March 17 (Box Box 407)
      - Federal Personnel. January - February, 1953, 1953 April 9 (Box Box 407)
      - Release - Correspondence between General MacArthur and Senator Byrd on the ammunition in Korea, 1953 April 24 (Box Box 407)
      - Byrd Budget, 1953 April 27 (Box Box 407)
      - Federal Personnel. February - March, 1953, 1953 May 4 (Box Box 407)
      - Release - On the ammunition shortages in the armed services particularly in Korea, 1953 May 23 (Box Box 407)
      - In connection with pasaage of Single Appropriation Bill in Senate, 1953 May 26 (Box Box 407)
      - Regarding Andrews Air Field as an auxiliary Washington airport, 1953 May 27 (Box Box 407)
      - Unexpended Balances, 1953 June 3 (Box Box 408)
      - Federal Personnel March - April, 1953, 1953 June 4 (Box Box 408)
      - On the passing of Dr. Douglas S. Freeman, 1953 June 15 (Box Box 408)
      - On the death of Senator Willis Smith, 1953 June 26 (Box Box 408)
      - Remarks on Rochambeau Pageant to be read by Charles Parmer, 1953 June 27 (Box Box 408)
      - Statement given to the Richmond News Leader on the fiscal situation, 1953 June 27 (Box Box 408)
      - Unexpended Balances, 1953 June 28 (Box Box 408)
      - Civilian Employment. April - May, 1953, 1953 June 29 (Box Box 408)
      - Remarks on the charges by J. B. Matthews of the McCarthy Committee, 1953 July 10 (Box Box 408)
      - Message to Hon. Tom Stanley on the result of the Primary, 1953 July 14 (Box Box 408)
      - Memorandum on the fiscal outlook, 1953 July 16 (Box Box 408)
      - On the liquidation of the R. F. C., given to Frank Taylor, 1953 July 26 (Box Box 408)
      - Statement praising Hon. Walter Robertson, telephoned to News Leader, 1953 July 27 (Box Box 408)
      - Civilian Employment. June, 1953, 1953 July 28 (Box Box 408)
      - Federal Funds, 1953 August 7 (Box Box 408)
      - Federal Personnel. June - July, 1953, 1953 September 7 (Box Box 408)
      - Statement relative to testimony of Beardsley Ruml on tax repeal and budget change, 1953 September 21 (Box Box 408)
      - On Unexpended Balances in federal appropriations, 1953 October 12 (Box Box 408)
      - Dalton Bond Proposal. (Folder empty when processed), 1953 October 21 (Box Box 408)
      - On the new airplane carrier, Newport News, Va., 1953 October 26 (Box Box 408)
      - Statement given to Roanoke World News on Virginia's Highway System, 1953 October 26 (Box Box 408)
      - Statement given to the Valley Papers on the road bond issue, 1953 October 29 (Box Box 408)
      - Winchester, Virginia, on the gubernatorial campaign, 1953 October 29 (Box Box 408)
      - Gubernatorial Campaign material, 1953 October (Box Box 408)
      - Federal Personnel. November, 1953, 1954 January 9 (Box Box 408)
      - On the awarding of the contract for the new super carrier, 1954 February 2 (Box Box 408)
      - On opposing bill pending to reduce taxes on liquor, 1954 March 9 (Box Box 408)
      - Tax Reduction, 1954 March 17 (Box Box 408)
      - On the death of Junius Fishburn of Roanoke, Va., 1954 March 24 (Box Box 408)
      - Re: Veterans' Benefits, 1954 April 2 (Box Box 408)
      - Statement upon introducing a bill making it unlawful to grant benefits and rights to persons not loyal to the U. S. Government, 1954 April 2 (Box Box 408)
      - On the investigation of the Federal Housing Administration, 1954 April 13 (Box Box 408)
      - On the F. H. A., 1954 April 20 (Box Box 408)
      - Letter to Mr. Cole, Administrator of Housing and Home Finance Agency, 1954 May 3 (Box Box 408)
      - Statement given to Mr. Frank Kent on "Why Admit Hawaii", 1954 May 3 (Box Box 408)
      - On turning over to Justice Department information on the F. H. A., 1954 May 7 (Box Box 408)
      - On F. H. A., 1954 May 12 (Box Box 408)
      - On the death of Senator Clyde Hoey, 1954 May 12 (Box Box 408)
      - On the decision of the Supreme Court to abolish segregation in public schools, 1954 May 17 (Box Box 408)
      - Report of Joint Committee on Civilian Employment in the Executive Branch, 1954 May 18 (Box Box 408)
      - On Amendments to the housing bill, 1954 June 2 (Box Box 408)
      - Federal Personnel and Pay. April, 1954, 1954 June 5 (Box Box 408)
      - On the housing amendment to the tax bill, 1954 June 9 (Box Box 408)
      - Statement issued with others on the Reciprocal Trade Agreements program, 1954 June 12 (Box Box 408)
      - Federal Housing Programs, 1954 June 28 (Box Box 408)
      - Tax Bill, 1954 August 5 (Box Box 408)
      - Debt Limit - not released, 1954 August 5 (Box Box 408)
      - On the Federal Housing Programs, 1954 August 13 (Box Box 408)
      - F. H. A., 1954 August 30 (Box Box 408)
      - Statement by the Joint Committee on Non-essential Expenditures. Federal Housing. (Folder empty when processed), 1954 September 9 (Box Box 408)
      - F. H. A. Windfalls, 1954 September 28 (Box Box 408)
      - On the low rent public housing, 1954 October 25 (Box Box 408)
      - Statement on the Forrestal, given to the Daily Press, Inc., Newport News, Va., 1954 December 2 (Box Box 408)
      - Federal Budget, 1954 December 7 (Box Box 408)
      - Minor Statements, 1954 (Box Box 408)
      - On the President's message, given to John Leard of the Richmond News Leader, 1955 January 6 (Box Box 409)
      - On the proposed new road plan, 1955 January 15 (Box Box 409)
      - Report of Joint Committee on Federal Civilian Employment. (Folder empty when processed), 1955 January 21 (Box Box 409)
      - On the passing of Henry D. Perkins, 1955 January 25 (Box Box 409)
      - In the Senate on Investigation of Federal Housing Administration, 1955 February 1 (Box Box 409)
      - On College Housing Program, 1955 February 4 (Box Box 409)
      - On increasing Congressmen's salaries, 1955 February 17 (Box Box 409)
      - On the New Housing Legislation, 1955 February 25 (Box Box 409)
      - On the item veto, 1955 March 2 (Box Box 409)
      - On the Single Appropriation Bill, 1955 March 4 (Box Box 409)
      - Federal Personnel and Pay. January, 1955, 1955 March 5 (Box Box 409)
      - On Senator's bill to repeal part of the law limiting the amount of wheat a farmer can grow, 1955 March 11 (Box Box 409)
      - Tax Bill, 1955 March 14 (Box Box 409)
      - Tax Bill, 1955 March 16 (Box Box 409)
      - Highway Statement - Public Works Committee, 1955 March 18 (Box Box 409)
      - On the passing of Col. Robert McCormick, 1955 April 1 (Box Box 409)
      - Joint Committee on Reduction of Non-essential Federal Expenditures on the housing program, 1955 April 21 (Box Box 409)
      - Joint Committee on Reduction of Non-essential Federal Expenditures on Personnel, 1955 May 2 (Box Box 409)
      - On Wherry Housing Projects, 1955 May 2 (Box Box 409)
      - On the so-called Columbus Circle slum clearance project, 1955 May 10 (Box Box 409)
      - On being re-elected Chairman of the Joint Committee on Reduction of Non-essential Federal Expenditures, 1955 May 10 (Box Box 409)
      - On the Clay Plan Amendment to the Highway Bill, 1955 May 25 (Box Box 409)
      - On the Reciprocal Trade Bill, 1955 June 7 (Box Box 409)
      - Report of Non-essential Federal Expenditures Committee on Federal Employment for May, 1955, 1955 June 30 (Box Box 409)
      - Mutual Security Appropriation Bill - Foreign aid, 1955 July 22 (Box Box 409)
      - Report of the Joint Committee on Reduction of Non-essential Federal Expenditures, 1955 August 1 (Box Box 409)
      - Statement on the 84th. Congress, 1955 August 2 (Box Box 409)
      - Balancing the budget, 1955 August 26 (Box Box 409)
      - Joint Committee on Reduction of Non-essential Federal Expenditures, 1955 September 2 (Box Box 409)
      - In tribute to the Boy Scouts of America, 1955 September 12 (Box Box 409)
      - Segregation, 1955 November 1 (Box Box 409)
      - On Federal Personnel for October, 1955 by the Committee on Reduction of Non- essential Federal Expenditures, 1955 November 30 (Box Box 409)
      - On the Referendum, 1955 December 18 (Box Box 409)
      - Minor Statement, 1955 (Box Box 409)
      - On the President's State of the Union Message, 1956 January 5 (Box Box 409)
      - Foreign Aid, 1956 January 5 (Box Box 409)
      - Amendment to the Federal Gasoline Law, 1956 January 13 (Box Box 409)
      - On the 1957 Budget Message, 1956 January 16 (Box Box 409)
      - Report of Joint Committee on Reduction of Non-essential Federal Expenditures, 1956 January 16 (Box Box 409)
      - On the Constitutional Amendment for a Balanced Budget. S. J. Res. 126, 1956 January 25 (Box Box 409)
      - Federal Personnel and Pay for December 1955 Joint Committee on Reduction of Non- essential Federal Expenditures, 1956 January 30 (Box Box 409)
      - Report of the Joint Committee on Reduction of Non-essential Federal Expenditures, 1956 February 16 (Box Box 409)
      - Interposition, 1956 February 26 (Box Box 409)
      - Report of the Joint Committee on Reduction of Non-essential Federal Expenditures, 1956 March 6 (Box Box 409)
      - Remarks on the resignation of Senator Strom Thurmond from the Senate, 1956 March 7 (Box Box 409)
      - Declaration of Constitutional Principles, 1956 March 12 (Box Box 409)
      - On Taxes, etc., and presenting the suggested Byrd Budget, 1956 March 20 (Box Box 409)
      - Statement by the Joint Committee on Reduction of Non-essential Federal Expenditures, 1956 April 9 (Box Box 409)
      - Statement by the Joint Committee on Reduction of Non-essential Federal Expenditures, 1956 May 3 (Box Box 409)
      - Unexpended Balances in Foreign Aid, 1956 May 10 (Box Box 409)
      - On Senator's wheat amendment to the Farm Bill, 1956 May 18 (Box Box 409)
      - Federal Housing Programs, 1956 May 22 (Box Box 409)
      - Federal Housing Program, 1956 May 23 (Box Box 409)
      - On the Davis-Bacon Amendment to the Highway Bill, 1956 May 28 (Box Box 409)
      - Report of the Joint Committee on Reduction of Non-essential Federal Expenditures, 1956 June 5 (Box Box 410)
      - On school facilities Little Creek area near Norfolk, 1956 June 6 (Box Box 410)
      - On the establishment of the Blue Ridge Parkway, 1956 June 7 (Box Box 410)
      - Relative to General Accounting Office Audits of Federal Housing Programs. Letter from President Eisenhower, 1956 June 7 (Box Box 410)
      - Debt Ceiling, 1956 June 13 (Box Box 410)
      - On further military aid to Tito, 1956 June 29 (Box Box 410)
      - Statement of the Joint Committee on Reduction of Non-essential Expenditures, 1956 July 2 (Box Box 410)
      - On H. R. 7089 So-called Survivors' Benefit Bill, 1956 July 2 (Box Box 410)
      - On H. R. 11740, fixing statutory debt limit for fiscal 1957, 1956 July 3 (Box Box 410)
      - Statement by Committee on Reduction of Non-essential Federal Expenditures on Unexpended balances, 1956 July 12 (Box Box 410)
      - On remarks of Governor Harriman, 1956 July 13 (Box Box 410)
      - Burke Airport, 1956 July 19 (Box Box 410)
      - So-called Civil Rights Legislation, 1956 July 25 (Box Box 410)
      - Joint Committee on Reduction of Non-essential Federal Expenditures, 1956 July 27 (Box Box 410)
      - Relating to Joint Committee on Internal Revenue, 1956 August 2 (Box Box 410)
      - Federal Expenditures, Revenue and Taxes, 1956 August 24 (Box Box 410)
      - Federal Personnel and Pay, by the Joint Committee on Reduction of Non-essential Federal Expenditures, 1956 August 31 (Box Box 410)
      - On the Housing Program, 1956 September 28 (Box Box 410)
      - Statement prepared for the Hosiery Industry Weekly, 1956 September 28 (Box Box 410)
      - Letter in regard to R. E. A. taxation, 1956 October 22 (Box Box 410)
      - Federal Personnel and Pay, by the Joint Committee on Reduction of Non-essential Federal Expenditures, 1956 November 1 (Box Box 410)
      - On the Suez and European situation, 1956 November 9 (Box Box 410)
      - On the interest payments Great Britain owes the United States, 1956 December 10 (Box Box 410)
      - On the candidacy of Judge Almond, 1956 December 11 (Box Box 410)
      - Threatened action of a Federal Judge in Tennessee, 1956 December 26 (Box Box 410)
      - Statement given to the News Leader on the outlook for the incoming Congress, 1956 December 27 (Box Box 410)
      - Relative to Fast Amortization, 1956 December 30 (Box Box 410)
      - Statement by the Joint Committee on Reduction of Non-essential Federal Expenditures, 1956 December 31 (Box Box 410)
      - On the fact that tax reduction is not possible, 1956 December (Box Box 410)
      - Statement after meeting of Southern Senators to oppose change in rules of the Senate, 1957 January 2 (Box Box 410)
      - Budget, 1957 January 16 (Box Box 410)
      - Secretary Humphrey's Statement on the Budget, 1957 January 17 (Box Box 410)
      - Statement on Wheat to permit growers to feed to their livestock, S. 658, 1957 January 17 (Box Box 410)
      - Joint Committee on Reduction of Non-essestial Federal Expenditures, 1957 January 17 (Box Box 410)
      - Statement on the report of the Joint Committee on Reduction of Non-essential Federal Expenditures, 1957 February 4 (Box Box 410)
      - Statement on Item Veto, 1957 February 14 (Box Box 410)
      - Letter to the Director of the Budget, 1957 March 8 (Box Box 410)
      - Federal Personnel and Pay, 1957 April 1 (Box Box 410)
      - Statement relating to investigation by Finance Committee of our financial condition, 1957 April 12 (Box Box 410)
      - Federal Personnel, Joint Committee on reduction of Non-essential Federal Expenditures, 1957 May 2 (Box Box 410)
      - On the President's Budget Message, 1957 May 15 (Box Box 410)
      - Statement by the Joint Committee on Reduction of Non-essential Federal Expenditures, 1957 June 5 (Box Box 410)
      - Statement of the Joint Committee on Reduction of Non-essential Federal Expenditures. Unexpended Balances, 1957 June 11 (Box Box 410)
      - Statement on Report of Joint Committee on Reduction of Non-essential Federal Expenditures on Federal Grants-in-Aid, 1957 June 14 (Box Box 410)
      - On examination of fiscal and monetary policies, 1957 June 18 (Box Box 410)
      - Senator Byrd's questions to Secretary of Treasury Humphrey, 1957 June 20 (Box Box 410)
      - Federal Grants-in-Aid to States, 1957 June 30 (Box Box 410)
      - Statement by Joint Committee on Reduction of Non-essential Federal Expenditures on Federal Expenditures on Federal Personnel, 1957 July 1 (Box Box 410)
      - Statement at the conclusion of testimony by Secretary Humphrey before the Senate Finance Committee, 1957 July 12 (Box Box 410)
      - Report of the Joint Committee on Reduction of Non-essential Federal Expenditures on Federal Employment, 1957 August 2 (Box Box 410)
      - Rapid Amortization - H. R. 232, 1957 August 5 (Box Box 410)
      - Statement opening hearing of William McChesney Martin during Committee's examination of fiscal and monetary policies, 1957 August 13 (Box Box 410)
      - Appropriation and Expenditures Reductions, 1957 August 31 (Box Box 410)
      - On the survey of the Potomac River by the Corps of Engineers, 1957 August (Box Box 410)
      - On sending Federal troops into Arkansas to enforce school integration, 1957 September 25 (Box Box 410)
      - On failure to reduce federal expenditures, 1957 October 2 (Box Box 410)
      - Statement requesting information from Secretary Brucker and his reply, 1957 October 4 (Box Box 410)
      - Statement in response to inquiry from Time Magazine, 1957 October 4 (Box Box 410)
      - Statement by Mr. Menefee concerning Robert Whitehead, 1957 October 15 (Box Box 410)
      - Telephone interview with the Richmond News Leader in regard to a stepped-up missile program, 1957 November 8 (Box Box 410)
      - On the passing of Frank E. Gannett, 1957 November 26 (Box Box 410)
      - Statement by the Committee on Reduction of Non-essential Federal Expenditures, 1957 December 6 (Box Box 410)
      - Telephone interview given Richmond News Leader - 1958 Forecast, 1957 December 28 (Box Box 410)
      - Proposals for New and Expanded Programs - 1958 Budget Document, 1957 (Box Box 410)
      - Bringing up H. R. 11740, Fixing the Statutory Debt Limit for Fiscal year 1957 (Box Box 410)
      - Commenting on the Federal Budget, 1958 January 13 (Box Box 411)
      - Statement by the Joint Committee on Reduction of Non-essential Federal Expenditures, 1958 January 23 (Box Box 411)
      - Statement by the Joint Committee on Non-essential Federal Expenditures, 1958 February 1 (Box Box 411)
      - Statement by Senator Announcing that he would not be a candidate for re- election, 1958 February 12 (Box Box 411)
      - Articles relating to Senator Byrd's statement that he would not seek re- election, 1958 February 12 (Box Box 411)
      - Resolution adopted by the General Assembly, re: Byrd's statement that he would not seek re-election, 1958 February 13 (Box Box 411)
      - In regard to the Senate Finance Committee's approval of increase in the debt limit, 1958 February 20 (Box Box 411)
      - Statement that Senator Byrd had reconsidered his decision to retire from the Senate, 1958 February 25 (Box Box 411)
      - Letter to Senator McNamara on changing the appearance of the U. S. Capitol, 1958 March 4 (Box Box 411)
      - Statement by the Joint Committee on Reduction of Non-essential Federal Expenditures, 1958 March 10 (Box Box 411)
      - Re: "The Power of Prayer", 1958 March 28 (Box Box 411)
      - Statement by the Committee on Reduction of Non-essential Federal Expenditures, 1958 March 31 (Box Box 411)
      - Statement by Mr. B. M. Baruch and inserted in the Congressional Record by Senator Byrd, 1958 April 1 (Box Box 411)
      - On the passing of Mr. Frank Kent, 1958 April 14 (Box Box 411)
      - Statement by the Joint Committee on Reduction of Non-essential Federal Expenditures, 1958 April 22 (Box Box 411)
      - Statement by the Joint Committee on Reduction of Non-essential Federal Expenditures, 1958 May 17 (Box Box 411)
      - On Federal deficit for fiscal 1958, Joint Committee on Internal Revenue Taxation, 1958 May 28 (Box Box 411)
      - In regard to railroad legislation, 1958 June 27 (Box Box 411)
      - Statement prepared for U. S. Chamber of Commerce, 1958 July 8 (Box Box 411)
      - Report of the Joint Committee on Reduction of Non-essential Federal Expenditures, 1958 July 9 (Box Box 411)
      - On the passing of Chief Justice Edward W. Hudgins, 1958 July 30 (Box Box 411)
      - Statement by Joint Committee on Reduction of Non-essential Federal Expenditures, 1958 July 31 (Box Box 411)
      - On the Jenkins-Keogh Bill, H. R. 10, 1958 August 7 (Box Box 411)
      - On Report of Joint Committee on Reduction of Non-essential Federal Expenditures, 1958 August 14 (Box Box 411)
      - Federal Budget - Debt Ceiling, 1958 August 15 (Box Box 411)
      - Re: Quemoy, 1958 October 5 (Box Box 411)
      - Expressing appreciation for re-election, 1958 November 5 (Box Box 411)